NATASHIA WHITE

CONTACT

65161 SW Smokey Butte Bend, OR 97703 (541) 639-1034 tashiaw245@gmail.co m whitenat.github.io

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Python
- C++
- HTML
- CSS
- Basic Web & Game Development
- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- Microsoft Office

RELATED COURSES

- Orientation to
 Computer Science
- Game
 Development
- Graphic Design

REFERENCES

Allison Bell, Bistro 28/ Bad Wolf Bakery — Manager 757.879.2799

OBJECTIVE

In my many years of experience in customer service, I've acquired the ability to collaborate and work with others and quickly learn new skills and procedures. I'd like to bring these abilities to new opportunities so as to broaden my skills set and build upon my personal interests and academic studies in computer programming.

EDUCATION

Oregon State University-Cascades, Bend, OR B.S. in Computer Science, Anticipated: June 2020 Focus in Web and Mobile Software Development

Central Oregon Community College, Bend, OR Associate of Arts Oregon Transfer, Graduation: June 2015

EXPERIENCE

Barista

The Lemon Tree, Bend, OR, August 2018 - Present
Bad Wolf Bakery and Bistro, Bend, OR, February - June 2018
Benny's Donuts, Corvallis, OR, September 2016 - June 2017
Francesco's Gelato, Corvallis, OR, September 2016 - June 2017

- Communicate with and inform customers of products
- Manage time to balance customer orders with prep work
- Collaborate with team in a fast-paced work environment
- Encourage customers to purchase up-sell items

Server/Hostess

Bistro 28, Bend, OR, June - September 2018

La Magie, Sisters, OR, June 2018 - February 2018

- Organized floor chart to maximize restaurants capacity
- Planned out reservations to efficiently fill the restaurant
- Communicated with customers in a friendly and professional manner to ensure satisfaction
- Collaborated with team members to balance the workload
- Learned quickly and cross-trained in various areas